{
    "subject": "resource/The_Disco_Boys",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Hamburg",
    "human_readable": "The Disco Boys are from Hamburg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9203036427497864,
            "question": "Is Hamburg the hometown of The Disco Boys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7030931115150452,
            "question": "Where are The Disco Boys from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6631942987442017,
            "question": "Which band hails from Hamburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6208255887031555,
            "question": "From which location do The Disco Boys originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49988916516304016,
            "question": "Can you tell me a place The Disco Boys are from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46613022685050964,
            "question": "What city is associated with The Disco Boys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45268765091896057,
            "question": "Where are The Disco Boys originally based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4278483986854553,
            "question": "What is the origin city of The Disco Boys?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39455029368400574,
            "question": "In what city did The Disco Boys form?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2361098825931549,
            "question": "What is the hometown of The Disco Boys band?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Disco Boys are from Hamburg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7145_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what city did The Disco Boys form?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7145_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the origin city of The Disco Boys?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7145_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where are The Disco Boys originally based?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7145_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7145_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all five documents mention that \"The Disco Boys\" are based in Hamburg. This is stated explicitly in documents 3 and 4 (\"Their type of music is called 'disco house' but sometimes it goes as 'french house'. The Disco Boys consist of Raphael Krickow and Gordon Hollenga...\"). Additionally, document 6 mentions that \"The Hamburg, Germany-based The Disco Boys have been making waves...\" which further reinforces the fact that they are based in Hamburg."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that The Disco Boys are based in Hamburg, Germany, which supports the statement that they are from Hamburg."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}